<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rafed's Blog on RaBlog</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Rafed's Blog on RaBlog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rafed.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Happy Birthday to you</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/english-song-chords/happy-birthday-chords/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/english-song-chords/happy-birthday-chords/</guid><description>Happy ABirthday Eto youHappy EBirthday Ato youHappy A7Birthday dear DJohnnyHappy ABirthday Eto Ayou</description></item><item><title>তোমার জন্য নীলচে তারার একটুখানি আলো</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/bangla-song-chords/tomar-jonno-nilche-tarar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/bangla-song-chords/tomar-jonno-nilche-tarar/</guid><description>Dতোমার জন্য Eনীলচে তারার Bএকটুখানি F#mআলোDভোরের রং Eরাতে মিশে Bকালো F#m. . .Dকাঠ গোলাপের Eসাদার মায়া Bমিশিয়ে দিয়ে F#mভাবিDআবছা নীল Eতোমার লাগে Bভালো। F#m. . .Dভাবনা আমার Aশিমুল ডালে Eলালচে আগুন জ্বালেDমহুয়ার বনে C#mমাতাল হাওয়া Bখেলে।Dএকমুঠো রোদ Aআকাশ ভরা তারাEভেজা মাটিতে জলের নকশা করাDমনকে শুধু C#mপাগল করে Bফেলে।Dতোমায় ঘিরে Eএতগুলো রাত Bঅধীর হয়ে জেগে F#mথাকাDতোমায় ঘিরে C#mআমার ভালো Bলাগা । F#m. . .Dআকাশ ভরা Eতারার আলোয় Bতোমায় দেখে F#mদেখেDভালোবাসার পা-Eখি মেলে মন ভোলা-Bনো পাখা ।</description></item><item><title>About Author</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/author/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 02:07:31 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/author/</guid><description>I am John Doe. And I can confirm that this is the best theme ever!</description></item><item><title>Admin Panel</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/admin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 02:07:30 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/admin/</guid><description/></item><item><title>All Sections</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/sections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 02:07:30 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/sections/</guid><description/></item><item><title>How to win Judo competitions</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/posts/martial-arts/how-to-win-judo-competitions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/posts/martial-arts/how-to-win-judo-competitions/</guid><description>If you have a competition ahead and you have no idea how you should train, this guide is for you. These tips apply whether it&amp;rsquo;s for a dojo fight or a competition. However, this is mostly intended for beginners who do not have much experience with Judo fights and have upcoming contests.
5 ways to win a fight Before dreaming that you are getting the gold make sure you know the following ways that can make you victorious.</description></item><item><title>Judo: the gentle way</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/posts/martial-arts/judo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/posts/martial-arts/judo/</guid><description>Judo is a discipline that involves using grappling and leverage to unbalance the opponent.
Originating from Japan, Judo was founded by Jigoro Kano in 1882. Judo means gentle way. A Judo practitioner is called a Judoka. Famous practitioners include Ronda Rousey, Vladimir Putin, Naomi Watts, Theodore Roosevelt.
Judo is gentle because its techniques use the least amount of force but with maximum leverage. It can also be considered gentle as no throws in Judo are done against the joints of the body.</description></item><item><title>Karate: The way of the empty hand</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/posts/martial-arts/karate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/posts/martial-arts/karate/</guid><description>Karate is a martial art discipline that involves kicking, striking, and defensive blocking. It is practiced as an art (budo), self-defense and a sport.
Originating from Japan, Karate was founded by Gichin Funakoshi in 1902. Karate means empty hand. Although empty-handed techniques are practiced most of the time, occasionally weapons are practiced as well. A Karate practitioner is called a Karateka. Famous practitioners include Jean-Claude Van Damme, Jennifer Aniston, Luca Valdesi, Bill (superfoot) Wallace.</description></item><item><title>A brief introduction to martial arts</title><link>https://rafed.github.io/blog/posts/martial-arts/a-brief-introduction-to-martial-arts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rafed.github.io/blog/posts/martial-arts/a-brief-introduction-to-martial-arts/</guid><description>Since the beginning of civilization, people have fought and engaged in war. They devised techniques to take leverage over their opponents and be the victor. This is why the art of fighting started to form and evolve. However, all martial arts did not evolve in the same way. Some focused on health benefits, some focused on spiritual aspects. Some focused on instant kills, and some focused to hurt as least as possible.</description></item></channel></rss>